ZACHARY B. DEACON

EXPERIENCE

Executive Director of Housekeeping at Hyatt Regency Bellevue

October 2017-May 2020

- · Managed a diverse team of 90 colleagues, including assistant managers which I promoted out into other leadership roles within the hotel.
- · Worked together with other department headers to improve metrics across all aspects of the hotel.
- ·Handled multiple large projects simultaneously
 - o Handled all budgeting, inventory and ordering
 - o Scheduling multiple staffing pools each week
 - Weekly payroll processing and creating/developing different incentive programs to motivate my team
 - o Colleague engagement
 - o Productivity management
 - o Interpreting and responding to guest feedback
 - o Learning and optimizing multiple operating systems
 - One on one development coaching and training of direct management staff
- ·Was given Manager of the year award in this role for my work in 2019:
 - o I increased our customer review scores by 300 basis points year over year
 - o I was able to decrease our hours worked per occupied room
 - I increased our year over year engagement scores of my direct reporting colleagues
- · Additional hotel wide roles:
 - Holiday Party Planning Committee
 - o Hyatt's Wellness Champion Program
 - o Associate Relations Committee
 - o Customer Service Improvement Team

Assistant Executive Housekeeper at Hyatt Regency Bellevue

- February 2017-October 2017
- \cdot After 8 months as an assistant I was able to promote into the department head role as Executive Housekeeper
- ·Learned to schedule a large team of 90 colleagues
- ·Managed the department's monthly budgets, keeping track of inventory and ordering supplies
- ·Played a large role in keeping the team motivated and engaged through projects, incentives and team building
- \cdot Tackled larger projects, planning and executing international housekeeping week, developing and managing a hotel wide renovation team

Assistant Front Office Manager Hyatt at Olive 8

Dec 2015-February 2017

- · Managing the front office and guest services teams and completing weekly schedules
- ·Coached and developed a team of 15 agents
- ·Learned to work closely and communicate effectively with other departments within the hotel to understand how I can help them to succeed
- · Created incentives and found new and creative ways to motivate my team through one on one development, detailed tracking of service scores, bulletin board projects, etc.

PROFILE:

I am an experienced, driven, hardworking operations leader with a diverse employment background. I thoroughly enjoy developing, training and leading teams to success while keeping colleagues engaged and energized. I pride myself in being adaptive to business demands and having an ability to connect with people of all backgrounds.

CERTIFICATIONS AND ACCOMPLISHMENTS:

- -EF Customer Service Training Workshop - May 5, 2011
- -Hyatt Regency Bellevue:
- Manager of the quarter 4th quarter 2019
- · Manager of the Year 2019
- -Situational Leadership 2 Certification (The Ken Blanchard Co) – September 2018
- -Lean Six Sigma (Yellow Belt)
- -Google Professional IT Support Certification

CONTACT:

PHONE: (206) 909-7450

EMAII.

zackdeacon347@gmail.com

REFERENCES:

Lance Marrin General Manager Hyatt Regency Bellevue Lance.Marrin@hvatt.com (425) 698-4205

Sean Clark Director of Operations Hyatt Regency Bellevue Sean.Clark@hyatt.com (530) 721-2736

Alex Dantes Director of Operations Hyatt Regency Dallas Alex.Dantes@hyatt.com (773) 457-1600

Joshua Starr **Assistant Director of Operations** Hyatt Regency Bellevue Joshua.Starr@hyatt.com (512) 538-4428

EXPERIENCE

Front Office Supervisor Grand Hyatt Seattle

May 2015-December 2015

- ·Built further on roles as a front office host and within 6 months was promoted to assistant front office manager
- ·Focused on making meaningful connections with my team and keeping everyone engaged during very busy months
- · Given the opportunity to work MOD shifts as a supervisor and learned to manage without direct oversight

Front desk agent Hyatt at Olive 8

April 2014-May 2015

- · Worked in providing the best customer service to guests in a fast-paced environment
- ·Learned complex computer systems that are used to control the everyday transactions that take place in a hotel
- · Worked with my front office team to cooperatively tackle the daily obstacles at the hotel
- ·Strove to be a leader at the front desk, and to help motivate the team to greater achievements
- •Duties include: Checking people in and out of the hotel, answering the phones, making reservations, helping with bell services, providing above and beyond customer service, upselling guests, promoting Hyatt's Gold Passport program, maintaining a high check-in score, etc.

Full time Sales Manager at Target Mobile

April 2012-April 2014

- · Showed success in meeting daily sales goals in a competitive, commission-based environment
- · Learned to manage and operate multiple complex computer systems
- · Managed opening and closing the store, inventory and shipping items to/from the store
- · Managing my associates effectively while keeping a strong relationship with the Target employees we worked closely with

Web development

EDUCATION

Shelton High School Shelton, Washington High School Diploma

South Puget Sound Community College Olympia, Washington Associates of Arts degree

University of Washington Coding Boot Camp Seattle, Washington **Technical Certificate of Completion**

SKILLS

Microsoft Suite Operating Systems Guest Services Team Engagement Budgeting, inventory and ordering, accounting and Binary P&L Javascript Project Management HTML Interviewing, hiring, coaching, developing CSS Payroll and scheduling SQL Productivity Management Js.node

Managing and responding to guest feedback

Team and office Management